Today we will talk about United India
Insurance Company Limited.
Many people had requested us to
make a video about United India Insurance and its competitive insurance policies. I will bring to you the review of all four
insurance companies, United New Indian
National Oriental.
Kavya Sandhya Kumkum does this.
Before starting with United India Insurance Company Limited, we
should give a little background about United India
Insurance Company. United
India Insurance Company was incorporated
in 1948. In 1972, when the general insurance
business was started,
many companies came into existence. United India
Insurance Companies also included 12
Indian Insurance Companies for Cooperative
Insurance Business and five Indian
Operations for Business.
United India Insurance Company
Limited was created by mixing these. You know that United
Insurance is controlled
by the Government of India and its operations are
managed by the Home Ministry of Finance.
So, this is a complete insurance
company and if we do a claim on it, then the
claim settlement ratio is approximately
2%.  Camera Suryavanshi Temple Sand and
Tiles Network which is
more than one hospital in West UP today we
will talk about their product
named Family Mediclaim Policy so see
this product has four features what is the
eligibility criteria what is it news what is it
not and what is the team so
before starting the video I would like to introduce myself
my name is Drink Warm
Gussa Financial Planner I bring such videos in front of every person
which makes your
personal life insurance bank jani easy
because our company's
tagline is creating verification
names so let's do the video United India
Insurance Company Limited's plan Sanwali
Medical Policy Good morning let's
see the eligibility criteria i.e. which oil is this policy if you are between ATM to truth
then you can follow this
and you can follow the quality of life
even after 65 so there is no definition here that itself when children keep
one thing in mind if you are entering
education ki distance senior
after gas policy mother then
temple run  It is payment which means
you will share 10% of the previous amount. Let's
move ahead, the children's pension is from
9110 to 1000.
After the completion of the period, the children will be given pension
and if they get married or get
married, otherwise the
26th child can continue the policy through ATM.
Vitamin solution is possible in New Zealand or Unemployed and Unmarried policy. Now
in the mid term policy, you can add a family member
on tax basis, which means for the
time of your policy duration, you
can add a premium and a family member. So, there can be two
ways in this, one is
newly married person, he can enter it
in the policy but within 7 days of marriage, not
after that, I don't want any candidate
from 1922 minutes. At this time, there is a 'Should not relate to any
file loss' option. You can use submit for
free leg for last five likes.
Share life it's my life style st0p.
In this, you can choose any MS Word.
Samlipta policy is available for Gwalior,
they will take this policy and keep reviewing it.
Now let's talk about the kind of papads
Kunwar is doing for Congress. First of all,
what is the room rent eligibility? How much is
eligible? If you have a policy below 5 lakhs, then there
is a deduction of 1% on room rent and
review means eight per cent of the mixture will be
given, it will not be given above that.
Secondly, if the policy is from pilot to a small panel, then
your room rent eligibility is formed
front of me shirt and single private
nursing home specialist can use it as per their wish.
Now we will talk about ICU ID
room. If the policy is below
5 lakhs, then two per cent of the mixture will be given. If the policy is above 5 lakhs, then it will actually be done
on it.
Now we will talk about the submission on some treatments, what are
those submissions, like if cancer
is on track and press enter at that
time and maximum cases
cannot be taken above that. Second, there are some sub
limits of mental illness treatment, if
mental due to which infection
hospitalization occurs, that means if
hospitalization occurs, that too  There is a
restriction for that which is capable. 1. Scent
of mixture on the face, maximum relaxed look, mosquitoes will
breed, crops standing on the road can be taken
but maximum select America, which are these
missions, there are 600 categories,
bipolar disorder, depression, upset compulsive
disorder, psychosis, if you get any
treatment done in this, then 20% and always maximum
selection policy, see this, treatment, treatment, polythene carry
bags,
you know what is treatment, now hospitalization is done on
request from the court,
which is done due to advancement of technology,
line of
treatment is surgery, all that is done, so
your pedicure, Team India's ODI
and test wise word and you
can understand its real meaning, keep in mind in this,
in the definition, they ask this question that if
I get a test done, if I get a diagnostic test done, then is it
covered, pregnancy
test is not a problem, it only has
proper treatment power, some
treatment is being done, the biggest reason is first, then
cataract surgery is
done in update, for that you should have a passport
but the amount is incurred which  Earlier, people used to
stay in hospital on the basis of caste and religion
after surgery in quarters, now they go in the morning and
come home in four to five hours, so see,
if you should understand the treatment in simple terms, then
admission and discharge is compulsory, only then
you will fight the exit poll, prevent
post and till live session, trial court,
hospitalization happens, before going to hospital,
four tests are done for check sciences and later tension,
only then you get admitted,
even after coming home from hospital, some medicines
are subscribed, if friends need consultation then that
too takes a turn, it will last for 30 days
and maximum 20% off of serial talk,
Mission AYUSH treatment is also of the birthday of AYUSH,
Ayurvedic, Unani, Siddha and
Homeopathy, if its hospitalization
habits, the body gets affected by drinking medicine, then keep this thing in
mind that every insurance policy has
this plan, Medical Unit
Certificate, if it is not medically necessary, that is,
treatment can be done in OPD, then
as soon as hospitalization is not done for it, then the
insurance does not give the claim
and secondly, what happens to those who have blend
superheroes, then what was reasonable, today
family treatment has been launched in other hospitals.  The
more you go, the more you will be given cream,
so the more Kabaddi impression hospitalization of Ayush treatment, if there is
no soft and window then its excision up to
harvesting news, till that organ
transplant is done then the
most in every quality is that we are a mixer, for
this I will create a Twitter in detail in the thread
and ginger policy while contacting the donor,
what all is there in it, how is the organ
donor transplanted institutional, that thing
mission road ambulance emergency road
ambulance, this is the news, point
five percent of always maximum 2508 means you will get
only ₹5 once for one
hospitalization, second on hair, Santosh
Someshwar maximum side from force policy, this
means in school you can change one percent of mixture or
maximum ₹5000 in a year,
not more than that, complimentary health
checkup is the last entry, from which you are given
if your three plans are these
and in every you will get
more according to your progress, then you will be helped
at a particular place, cent of mixed maximum
phase policy  For 1000 term
policy, it will not be decided on that
but screen chemistry
is necessary, meaning if you renew your policy today, then the
policy which you had continued for the last 3 years should be clean
free, there should not be any claim in it,
so come, you can click on that time table policy
80 floater policy,
next modern treatment unwanted
soldiers to modern treatment channel or
plastic surgery is converted in your policy,
absolutely all the limits are there, whenever there are
different treatments on the MS Word screen,
this Lakshman has been designed, so keep in mind
before getting the treatment that
you will not get the entire case of modern treatment,
now we will talk about this, these are your
inbuilt covers which are intimate in high quality, if
you want to take some optional kabaddi on it, it is
also called riders,
you can do that, what is optional constipation, then everything
whole fennel fenugreek and restoration and it
always happens that means if you always
art patil this defect happens then if it happens
on the resort, like here and
Vitamins will be exhausted and you will lose another time. The claim is
eligible for insurance. Hundred percent
of the amount is always for the next 10 lakh policy, so if the policy is for the next 10 lakh then
10 lakh will be restored. Therefore, there is a condition
in this policy that the
additional 10 lakh refilled again for unrelated reasons,
whether it is for unrelated reasons or any other,
cannot be explained by getting it from the insurance
and the maximum claim that you will make in one go will be
absolutely zero. So, a claim above 10 lakh will never be made for a single year.
In this policy, you all know that
if the remaining benefit is
not to be used by you, it is not carried forward in this year, it is
not carried forward in inactive form. The next optional
benefit which is side is maternity
units, if you do not want to get it done, you
can get it done. Look at this problem, there is a
waiting period of 24th March in this and there is another condition,
this also  Questions are asked in the marriage procession,
can I take quality for myself or can we take single person quality,
no, it is necessary to have lift qualities in this policy, so it is
necessary for both husband and wife to have it, if you want to
take the full war with maternity benefit, then this video channel will be
waited from the date when both are held in the policy,
from there 24 months will be accounted, then it will
stay for 24 months and there is a
cut in it, Pappu delivery or low fruit medical
termination happens, now along with that
comment, there is more gravity than calling honey,
if someone has children,
if the girl and more than two children are
invested, then in this you do not have the light to erase, there is no
competent authority benefit limit, you do
not always have the comment, so what
is the limit, tempered glass MS Word maximum 2004 will do
half from normal delivery, newborn baby, you want a
difficult policy, if you have a nice day, then
Noida will be better for change,
after the notice in the policy, you will have to take additional team and add, then
maximum job medical
expense in them  Game do coat stand
scent of misfortune special condition
semi toilet is unique that's why I am going to do it
I will tell you firstly this balance
is admissible if this treatment is infection
hospitalization if there is any
treatment of tension then there is no comment secondly there is
no news of locket pregnancy in this there is
any one where the volume is getting
their medical termination done
withdrawal difficulty of pregnancy tree then
also that is a commitment prenatal
post natal expenses are not commented in the policy if there is
no infection hospitalization then it is
linked with first if there is infection
hospitalization then only prenatal post
natal means the earlier expenses which are
consultation hot expenses before and after baby delivery
they will also not be commented
if there is no infection hospitalization and
one more thing which we show for the rates of
TDS we prevent hospitalization
class that is also not available in this
because the previous limit is a patient of chilli
and peas in this there is maximum 20
For tournaments also, you cannot take an airplane in the form of poison
paint like Someshwar Prenatal Possible To
Intimidate Infrequent Hospitalization
Expenses,
next is Hospital Cash Withdrawal,
that is also called this, it means that
insurance companies
give additional tax benefit for the number of days you stay in the hospital, it is different from this, so for a
policy
more than Rs. 500, you will be given Rs. 500 for that number of days, maximum you
can do Rs. 5000,
if you have a policy, you can do
thousands of rupees maximum every day,
if you can subscribe for 15 to 20 rupees,
but it will be donated, that is, you
can screen, now let's talk, the
most important part is that I have told you this, would
you know, then automatically, leaving that,
everything is covered, then there is never any
disappointment, so firstly, if the
waiting period is clear, then it is of 30 days, that is the
duty, friend, you
cannot get hospitalization done, whereas
accidental  We will add power with emergency. If
pre-existing is serious then
send a pre-existing email message that from here basically
you should make a detailed video of this before taking the policy
so that they will not discuss it.
Through this, do
two different things here, so
let's see that
you can see this in front of you, you
can do this of Sonth,
if you can see in front of you then if you take
care of these things then there will never be any disappointment at the time of cleaning
that this
screen did not match, that did not match, if
this is not Kabaddi then Shahrukh will not be
given insurance, so take special care of these things,
please watch it carefully and
understand it carefully,
you can change any question regarding science
in the comment section and then comes the 5 minute
accident which is prominently
not mentioned in the policy, this is generally what happens,
I have made a detailed video of many points,
you can check what
I am talking about, I will attach the 2018 PDF with you,
now the policy
description  You can also do this in that,
next its premium calculation, so this
cream cream is completed now,
according to the dot, the rates on these were, then your zone
comes in Delhi NCR,
Faridabad, Gurugram, Palwal, Rohtak, Jhajjar, Gautam
Budh Nagar, Ghaziabad, Bulandshahr, this comes in
your zone in Delhi-NCR, then
Mumbai City, Mumbai City,
Mumbai Suburban, 9th,
Gujarat, there are some state news
in both, which are Ahmedabad, Gandhinagar,
Surat, Vadodara, so this was the slide written by me of
United India Insurance Company,
so I am trying to cover all the points of this year,
you can refer to it, you
can see it before taking the policy, there is no suitable helpline for you, if you have
any question,
you can ask by recording this line, we
can type another one, our phone number,
email ID is mentioned, now if you want to save it on the policy through us, you can
contact us, there is a possibility of it, before leaving, a
reminder, if you have not subscribed to my channel yet, do
Subscribe to be
divided always meet on the other side
next till then
before starting on the specific side let's go to end 5
about the video so close the two
shoulders a
who is so this has
happened